# **Robert Wagner** | UI/UX Designer

Salt Lake City, UT

rob.wagnerusa@protonmail.com | LinkedIn Profile | Portfolio Website | C. 385.495.4015

### **Professional Summary**

**About Me** | Dynamic background in Communications, Sales & Marketing, Education, and Technical Support with 20+ years of combined professional experience.

Why UI/UX Designer | With a degree in Web Design and Development, broad professional background, and a passion for customer experience, and team collaboration, I naturally gravitated to the UI/UX side of Web Development, and love designing Websites/apps with that goal in mind (See examples)!

### **Skills & Experience**

- Coding Languages | HTML, CSS, Javascript, and PHP
- Software | Adobe PhotoShop, InDesign, Illustrator & Premier. Figma. MS Word, Excel, Outlook+
- Style Guides | Can follow a Style Guide, and deeply enjoy the branding and UX process of it
- Communication | Advanced written and verbal communications at all company levels
- Customer Service Expert | 20+ years in broad Customer Service environments
- Team Building | Passionate about building a positive environment (See Utah First Credit Union)
- Public Speaking | Delivered 1,000's of career presentations, and conducted 100's of interviews
- UX Sample | Word Press Example Site (took about 1 hour, very simple construction co. site)
- UX Sample | <u>Built-from-scratch website</u> as a community volunteer on Emergency Preparedness

## **Employment**

**Applications Support Engineer II** MVi - Millennial Vision, Inc.

2018 - 2024

MVi/CDi provides SaaS Solutions for Financial Institutions and Municipalities in Electronic Content Management systems, including hardware and software deployment, configuration, and support.

- Built online form (Laserfiche Forms) to serve as Annual Review Form for the entire company
- Built multiple LF Forms for customers' electronic document processing needs on many levels
- Configured Workflows to help process documents automatically per conditions and field values
- Updated customers' logo with brand changes to support a better UX for their team
- Simultaneously manage between 10-20 projects, coordinating with all levels of a company from C-Suite Execs to front-line staff, in achieving goals on time in our IT Project Management vertical
- Completed 30+ contracts in 2023, securing \$300K+ in company revenue

- **Productivity** | Fast-paced, solutions-driven, objectives achieved. Sometimes solving 100+ tickets/month where it was common for team members to achieve between 40-60
- **UX Design** | Also served as a local website resource, responsible for adding documents, and managing updates/menus with UX of company website

#### Recruiting Manager | Robert Half

2017

Robert Half provides talent sourcing services for Finance and Accounting roles, as well as Technical and other business process roles

#### **Assistant Branch Manager** Utah First Federal Credit Union

2016-2017

- Design | Designed a branch-specific marketing slick, and used it to prospect local dealerships
- Sales | Added 3 new dealer partners to the branch the same week and began taking applications
- Team building | Reduced branch turnover from 75% to 25% by analyzing the team's
  motivations/interests, providing regular branch snacks (on my own dime, but worth it), as well as
  a positive, upbeat attitude to help keep the team happy and engaged

#### **Field Admissions Representative** | Universal Technical Institute, Inc.

2012 - 2015

Universal Tech. provides technical career training for Automotive, Diesel, and motorsports industries.

As a Field Admissions Representative, I was invited into 50+ high schools to provide career planning presentations to classes of ~20-40 students

- **Public Relations** | Conducted 400+ interviews with students and their families to discuss their education & career path, and plan a course to help them achieve it
- Public Speaking | Delivered 1,000's of career planning presentations in High Schools
- **Productivity** | Generated over \$1,000,000 in successful starts my 2<sup>nd</sup> and 3<sup>rd</sup> years each.
- **B2B** and Education industry relations | Went from 15 active accounts to over 50 active accounts by conducting consistent follow up, professionalism, and demonstrating the value our career planning presentations deliver to their audience

Click to view **full employment** history

### **Education**

BS - Web Design & Development | BYU